{
    "id": "646cb114a3524a2fa7c9217244960aeb",
    "title": "Comparatives Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Your car is ………………… .. than mine.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more small",
                "smaller"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e40624a926074a8599ce91efd1ca03bc"
        },
        {
            "question": "My house is ……………………… than yours.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bigger",
                "biggest"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1c30116bd0034c3c9bf0942e9d044343"
        },
        {
            "question": "You should write ……………………… than you do.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "oftener",
                "more often",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b64d9da0efe048db814fe59e536fcabd"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is ………………… than you think.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "easier",
                "more easy"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e5ac7c54e60b4b769368e65ea93ad712"
        },
        {
            "question": "The baby is ………………… ugly than you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "lesser"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "89f6abe79bc14c138f0fbaaa7ad1a1c9"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have got …………………. energy than I used to have.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "fewer"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ef090c0dd1b84cf28d44c487191f2464"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is ……………………… than that.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "commoner",
                "more common",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "de2d474a41524a139c21e36045cc625f"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ………………….. than stupid.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more lazy",
                "lazier",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cb6ae1d6f6e94b7db672783e1c547dcd"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her boyfriend is ………………… than her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "much old",
                "much older",
                "more old"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "655c070102924852a229b3ba6d50963b"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ………………… than he looks.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "cleverer",
                "more clever"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8fcc3a751dd54e8d8f2ddb982e1f8f77"
        }
    ]
}